We're going to Alhaurín de Animales, I'm
gay,
I'm fine on the schedule, I
'm Mighty Singstar, and the story of
my, the story of my
teachings,
Fort and Ford, and that's 44 years ago, there are more than
20 that U2 keys, my teacher told me
that he lives and teaches a class in the wake, there are
clear ones, and I stood up to teach the
class
very well, it
gave me a lot of pity and sorrow,
like sowing the seed to be able to
talk about Nitro to me, and he taught me, Palito, I became accustomed to it, he
taught me too well, not in
peace, Bautista, which is impossible, what he did,
exhausted, titid, is that I'm going to
try to keep up with the
schedule of fools, the three of us, and not tell such
long stories,
throw wine, pyrolysis,
Western,
okay,
since neither Camacho, the stage,
and they can go up on the stage, okay,
des holding de sweet,
all the teachings of this week and
tongue twisters, it's about anger, disdain,
desire, or the night, and we gave all
the negative emotions, heart is top,
how to stop them, the best way to start,
ya, and the best way to study it  It's
Coudet Investments, it's called The Two
Husbands, know this morning, so this
morning, highlight of directives, Wind, I
would like to do The Two Husbands here, I say
here we go,
and
efe the cannabis hashish, if you're going to be a
master of Eisai
[Music],
and know The Two Husbands in the Kitchen
is very important, tourism is
that all Buddhism is in the kitchen,
the areas of gays, the guagua and elves
that Chente, some say gay, will it be because you
're doing this cooking thing, there's no
other that's called The
Husbands in the Kitchen, tesitura reading by
Pura, or you can remove the sutra written
by Buddha, it's only for the gay kitchen and
restore, indicate, has, wants, good
suture, if it's not a kitchen, it shouldn't
be in the substrate, that this post is
dessert, Sofia, lower pillar, because the others
are supposed to help you have
a happy life,
so everything from the sutra should be in the
kitchen, the whole kitchen should be more
versatile, subtes Howie, so he, all
week, Google Talk about Steve,
understands that we're going to talk about The Two
Husbands in the Kitchen,
the show is  The one that manages you and it takes
like 10 minutes to teach it at World
Vision and if you want to be teachers of Asia
I think this is the most important thing you
can learn
so here it goes it's the same has to do with me
and me waka if you want to make a video
do what I saw with show to the city of
Benares teacher ok you
have to learn how you have to
learn to teach it and the sag and being
here is how they start jaime typical
housewife
typical hashtag I am a
typical housewife in Guadalajara in Guadalajara
city are I am a
housewife wherever you are
the heart to kids then I have two children
their martinis and who are my children
let me tell you jordi markets
you want us services louis that
you and you this
ok I
have three children I have a job and I
work for an internal company of
nothing and there is no works hard work hard and
mona is an architect who is disco in
the morning I have to take my children to
school after work and health com
after work I have to go back to
Caja de Burgos I have to buy to
ratify the dear I have to pick up the
children yesterday  Roman to your CV and when I
get home I have to cook 16
vehicles are strongly this is a
very good system for men in
the past times to
dominate to work and made man and the man
worked and made the money to the women
at walking works and kits the woman had to
cook and take care of the children of water
they go
Leiber there was a division of labor of
managing meeting where it goes of we had
meeting then the men had a
meeting if you women don't know
we had it
and it's going to be a macabre plan has existed
women the world to work we have to tell
women that they have the right to
work since they love me and Martí that it's
better then they can make the
money take care of the children and cook
which was to work and we can watch
the World Cup that was played this xxv
export
this plan was successful - nothing women at the
right to make the man and now
women have the right to make
money from the art of taking away football
to the children and the food up typical women
I am a woman from Vicar district I have
these three children already going and I have a
husband  or that they are just as hard work so
one day at work looking for me
my boss arrives one and go home when I'm
going home Grammy
tells me to take tomorrow and allow a
very important meeting the Basque love
now you must arrive an hour before you
understand me if my ovaries
mean that if not you by cable of
run if you get here good time you have to
come an hour before ok ok
[Music]
water without decoration fernández I was
in the corporation for 19 years
attali starting bernstein I'm going to
tell you something very weird very strange
you can find minis late to work if you
arrive five minutes late to work I'll
pass and adagio the boss is going to yell at you
well pay classics cycle with this
old and then at five or six in the
afternoon when it's time to go home yell
that you didn't give fortune brands you can
stay two extra hours
[Music]
mini you can stay two more hours
but you can't arrive five minutes
late because there is no such thing as
this system you know there is only one glass that I
tell the boss ok
there is promise mouth I promise I'll go  to come
because then Hewitt and then
you have to negotiate with the children about
Kirchner more with the praises to the room to
the children if it's a tumor or children tomorrow
mommy heart and what to work and early mommy
has to go to work an hour earlier I
have to take them to school an
hour earlier
Scotti joke said that the teacher says it's
okay go on YouTube but
I need them to be ready
efe/yonhap see and if they're not ready and
mommy's read if mommy arrives late in Managua
that fire ama they're going to fire me eggs
Farfán and we're going to have a problem in the
family whose first promise me
and that tomorrow morning in April and they're going to be
ready an hour earlier you call oft
without pajamas school otan with the
school uniform their shoes also
laces tied in marketing and the
homework finished gray okay already of al
ayat mom tells me on top of that more if mom
even though tomorrow I arrive an hour early to the
room they're fighting each other
yelling because they still have their pajamas they have
n't put on their shoes because
when the homework is on the floor u2 and
amos  Topics are the same, the three
stupidest kids in the stadium then
they start crying
[Laughter] It
's mommy, I already know the topic, so the mom
yelled at them in static and they started
crying, why did they
hear the word "mom," the
word "mom" has in Paris, did
anyone else hear the negative bad word "
mom," "
mom," "I hear the negative bad word "
mom," and come on, they are the stupidest kids
in Guadalajara, work, every word, you are, you, you
are chapters, and they are
entering through mom's ear too,
touch my mind, and it touches mom's mind, and it
makes an
impression on mom's mind,
and two hours after fulfilling
that impression,
newt che collected when they teach it to
earn
and camps, and it becomes a seed
index smile in the subconscious mind,
enter the word impression of the bad
word in the ear,
we prick and it becomes a seed,
the karmic seed index of
ages main in the subconscious mind, mom
is the nec decides informal, now mom
has a negative seed in her mind
that  He claimed he doesn't die and goes to cook
in lament that in art one week
after a week to Miami homework I'm
arriving from work I arrive at the house
the vital I Aldo let me tell you jump in
Taiwan from Uruguay
Skype sometimes I wonder why I
married this guy and don't take away what's
the World Cup he just spends his time watching
the World Cup
art time they take and I have to make the money
by the walls and I have to buy the
groceries and techniques I discovered that I have to
take the children to school
pick them up and not art of art I have to
do everything there are two members white
America I don't remember why I married
him
[Music] he
still gives me some good hugs and then in
all Guadalajara daughter you know his
hugs are the best and coming what's
your mouth even though he spends his time watching the
World Cup that I'm going to show you just
like Samuel you arrive home from work
fat from kitchen you enter the kitchen open
the door open the door love I arrived
[Laughter]
it's difficult what it is to have older people and
they are too  something said
I arrived once again
yes yes
d
in addition how do you feel if no and it
was all on the web you
told your friend it's peratta that
you see two good hugs that you opened
the door for me
and you're like action
what's your natural reaction
[Music]
I just opened the door and
the zenith started yelling and I didn't say anything and this started
yelling at me someone united I didn't do anything
and it's been going very well they miss me
and that they're not here anymore and he started
yelling and said it's true
Jesse Chusid in Indiana it's true that he didn't do
anything no no it's true because if you already
let him yell at his kids the way
last week and for being on Gmail well
a seed in his middle weapons of the is
about God children more type test and he put the
seed that the seller gave me when he opened
the door I arrived syrup syrup the
seeds open it's already light up that only
like the feather all bird
[Music]
don't worry in Aguaytía they must pay
to seal the feather
half
without the old feather of a seed in your
mind the one from Canfranc and the feather doesn't
come  of the feather and it's in Canfranc
depends on you if it gets if the feather
came from the feather the dog would see a
feather in Davenport and the dog
would write poetry to the top of his
girlfriend [ __ ] and Otea is obvious said your tail
is very beautiful
there where but in the SE-30 it was found
that therefore the feather does not come from the
feather who song and the feather comes from
me in Dejas Bell and the husband touched me
stupid who calls me stupid bear
according also comes from my car form
as it comes from my Ayala tequilas I yelled
at the children the week passion stench watch I open
the we visit supplies do
slow motion
let's do it again
ok if Opel the seeds this
field opens comes from me that comes from me to
say open so the seeds open
and if to me and to me yells now we know
it and that when they teach it before was at
this point we visit and tactical formations and
this is the most important teaching of
Asia and then at this point in this
you hear Whitby funny and Letizia and  It's always good to
be funny in the teachings there's
SingStar I think Haiti sensitive to I
think Buddhism should be fun
make decisions you are don't be this
serious monster
and UGT Asturias you should ask the
public wire direction let's admit
time in question because you didn't
ask me the most important question
[Music]
you already the lies lie said x my
apology is the one that is seen because
you have the husbands I say it's illegal
because you have the husbands of new
bandages management pins and then 13 the
husbands here next to you
ok years guarantees plate and captures times and I'm
going to explain why I have two
husbands stop Phoenix they have
different names of those see this
husband is name is Mr. Ping his name
is Mr. Feather Mr. Feather Mr. Do you let me see
this champion husband comes
from my mast from my seed Watts and what
seed
White and Adam Smith and I yelled at my
boys to wear themselves out this champion husband
comes from my Mr. Feather Mr.
Feather already despairs now this husband of
Switch I fear that later the changes the
exchanges was this  husband bachis nor
what is his name that does not wish
of jasper listen this husband
also comes from the takeoff this feather
canfranc that comes from the feather ok avivar
and in the world textile champion of ping
all the people in the world believe that
the feather comes from probability
pitbull gamecube to wii tours and simple
only the people who have gone to a
good Buddhism class that came to
a good Buddhism class stop being
must confront understand that the feather
comes from them frank follow mine from
a seed in your mind
tishman this field comes to me from my visual
this
ltd menem and started yelling at me that
nothing web
you have to do what you do immediately after
the report very important that you do not
listen to one of this to spend
willy does one of these two husbands
really exist
as far as you know that he does not exist and
one of these two husbands cannot
exist until the east and then
ask the public with one
billy ex which really exists
already me this feather I know if Mr. Feather and
Excel he is and camp comes to me from my ok
field comes to me  age went up is real
the orchard husband puto link where is
the husband who doesn't exist visual this from
Canada and Taiwan and astound that impossible
invite in the world the hyper lord
open me all the objects in the world
all the people you have met
company justice come from your seeds
and look to be a leader in camp if you
meet someone who doesn't come from you and
an exam that doesn't exist you met
someone who can't exist that they avoid
cancer that everything comes from my uncle me and
you can are everything around you comes from
you type people without things world
countries
one geranium a hair on your head
avoid dissatisfied everything comes from you is
nothing untouchable there is nothing that doesn't come
from Texas but this husband with excess doesn't
exist to
teach the two husbands anp site and
if there is I am teaching them if there is more
time is from Haiti and the most
important teaching from Asia and Guarionex where they
go next and what to see and Ravi informs
quest is a very very important question
towards the East ask the public what
good from Quiche when  You enter the
kitchen Henares Meco and I was and the husband
you stupid and tactical sent and you
start to get angry which was see yesterday with
which exposed you got angry
which moon which
Benavides man this notice can't
be cool because watch what we
serve
[Music]
hello my name is syrup seeds and was
witness and here I put the seeds
with the nor the field comes from my pen
[Music]
that I shouldn't get angry again
when he called me stupid I should never
call him stupid
if he calls me stupid I call him stupid
tennis correct jms toupee then he's right
because I'm stupid
because Picasso ok come or not I was
not you're stupid
[Music]
Hartwig Ley Evin next week that's
alive
the kids are going to be manuals because you
picas aixec to the stupid because I said I
'm not stupid you're
stupid
now you can't go to do we love life
now we can go to the wheel of life
you can  constituted we can go to the
wheel of life
[Music]
I'm not stupid you're stupid
new family next week chubby student
week you go to the children's room and I
that's your skin they're stupid don't even see
if you plant a new bad seed
[Music]
and from now on they don't understand the wild life
that wheel of life snap
eating out wilbert it's not an
old painting from the Renaissance and aesthetics
it's a teaching about your home it's
of origin let's do it again
how to be wild life how to break the wheel
of life
this is the wall street this is the goal
of that room and tim godwin is the
only thing we're doing from teacher
juanita the objects options the
purpose of 20,000 pages of
translation self project how to break
how to stop this state saw how to stop
the wheel and they're ready I'm here
you're stupid
[Music]
okay
if james bolton there broke the wheel it's
more your throne pulverized the wheel that
eddie too I love you too next break little
story of the kid next week
when I go to the children's room
and  Europe, those beautiful children,
perfect YouTube, I love them too. I open
the door.
Dr. Rubio,
the now ex-queen, Start the Women
Zeppelin, it's very, very good to talk to
women. Besides, what they look at, this is
true.
All things are stupid.
All wives don't know everything,
but don't tell them they're going to make a
new bad seed,
the one of the beast, and that's all. It's about
their own exhibition, and that's the
purpose of starting and winning.
Tintin tourism, we're not teaching
Buddhism. Jaime King, Happy Feet, and we're
doing happy kitchens.
Adolfo Gay, don't forget that nothing was going on,
nothing I could feel. He's not a master of
Buddhism. Martin Happiness, they're teaching
happiness.
Okay, go. The resources,
you guys, organizational
Twitter allows more than empowers an
extension. Okay, the ex-corde of Lumen,
let's go to the garden.
[Music]
10,
this gray patent, what we stopped at
10:30, said
[Music]
to friends from Carmen, what we're going to do is go
hungry. This technical entity, Word,
this is the old technical book where
you find kitchen information. Where you
find information about  The
kitchen, this 'no negotiation' and I'm going to
go through every word, I'm going to review every
word, and it has foreign language, it's in
a foreign language, fact that's fine,
water, YouTube, and all that, that Chen Chih
-Chung song in Chantilly,
I want you to feel that the teaching of
the kitchen comes from the ancient teaching,
6 is already swift, so the strength of, and
if there is hysteria, commission, try, it's that it
comes from the ancient teachings, and it's
that Tintin doesn't admit bike, gay, and Marc,
this teaching of the kitchen wasn't made
by gay and Mike Ellis, made by Dura, it was
made by Buddha
in one, is the meaning of versions, word,
doubt, what is the meaning of the
word in Sanskrit, Buddha in my
depression,
things in all times, the time, means the
person who can see all things at
all times, in all times,
Wintour, distinguishable detractors,
walking street, day in one, when Doubt
gave this teaching, he was observing us
today in Guadalajara, okay, and world,
this book for the people, the day, he
wrote this book for the people
here today, shop and Bogota of
instinct, so we're going to go  to the
old books that have form wish is in a
foreign language don't worry about
phone don't worry make that decided
teacher and the chs in a by black swan
just relax and absorb like a sponge
that maya dressed in jean king my job
is to teach you
and here we go
[Music]
as he shouted s
and measurable of the series 7 four dollar sites
trafford alex jones
in 1
[Music]
the one of ok go down or of text
the we see
ok I'm going to
say freedom not for good
luck horowitz a white man and when and
sensing game
orbital means ok software hefner allows
an artist fire with in chimbo
so for half an hour every day they have to
suffer with the old book the way
back don't worry ok and nobody post is
not supposed to understand it
by bita wichita maric for ok guariste
blood of the circle of life what is the
root the origin of the circle of the cycle of
life to the collapse end the cycle of
suffering and choose maric for it is
called here richer and I do
n't  You understand the pen in giving classes to
kids on FM and that causes the problem in
your family YouTube match respè you
talk back to your husband but
Newbery not mine you put a new bad
seed in your mind the yoke of decision
passes to the room the children of Praxis open
the bad seed opens and Joe Buck
Tickets yells back at the children
and the Wild Staffing record and this is called
the wheel of suffering
also and everyone in this room mine
or I too mini art estate after
many years of studying management people
trouble with there are still people with
whom I have problems who use Pipo
Haiti you still and with problems that
bother me with people who annoyed me with my
tongue who make me angry that your
tie Begic Tamariz which not in short
Henkel in Game World with the line which
means that we were born with that
evil in  understanding of the training that knows
little children get in
insect sect or has waypoints we were
born a month before had to with the
misunderstanding of the pen and well
understand the pen even an ant I
can step graft you push with a little
piece of grass with a little strip of
grass and it's like someone
everyone gets and venage you even
the ant get annoyed with and they call me
has Paula and Tiguan and what an
android life of Maxi unhappy if you want to
eliminate that anger that makes you unhappy
so hand and hung mortally vision
that for the glue and a mask of
extending you must try to understand the
pen
when it's on the skin if you understand the
I was respective you're going to stop your
response to the husband Tom Ford don't
forget and if I was it's
stupid and if then but I didn't
tell him that nobody has it nor her
vehement hood if your taboo nor there for
this one magic and therefore there is a
magic pill a magic pill with
like or meadows lady that is going to stop
all the problems in your life which is the
same expression sprint is  like a
special aspirin in the trade and if you
take it every morning and Hugo Java
happiness you're going to have a happy life
what's the name of that pen aspirin
that feels like memory if you take it
every morning please jury member
nature in gray sad
art today to the leaves you'll probably
remember three days after you
yelled at your husband member in the
king it's very difficult to remember it in the
kitchen de Gaulle costumes the goal of
these classes is and remember the pain in
the kitchen is that you remember the pen in
the kitchen talk you walk you probably wo
n't you remember two days later
you'll remember two days later I
shouldn't have yelled at him text
aptitudes may of those two days later
I have costumes the goal of these classes
make times order in surf to be that
time span shorter and shorter
how you know it with Isner van a that is
my sister Marie Simon that is Miriam
Snap by James Bulger is not the same as
the deity of wolves
the venerable fil said this morning take
my sister means no for gamecube
nobody can make that  Don't get upset and the
present cake is 100% relaxed
factory in Mediaset nobody can make you
upset Estepona that's Nirvana
Hutsby Brothers I have three brothers
with fire and Rifai Minis we fight every
five minutes
Miley Libra from Goes to My Name
My little brother's goal is to make me
angry
he does everything possible to make me
angry and then he makes me angry and Laciana
and Baylee's Durban
if I reached my sister and Mike he's
in the chair and I'd be a Walker
and wouldn't get upset silly you'll take ANP
Height Deputation and I don't think Nirvana
is something very high only doubt can
be there from the
wave indec touch in Ruby members of
then it's
the wife who's in the kitchen and
remembers the pen and doesn't win is
back reached Nirvana the wind that
the moment camps when the
difficult moment arrives you leave crazy and stupid
and the husband calls you stupid take the
magic take the magic pill
mmm md remember the pen / going
maybe the dog always  They spent them
at the box world association store,
genius book montage with a lot of vision,
Bayern of knowing and firm,
this is a very famous author, code aie
theme is called area for Woods and
Stricker, who is their teacher
[Music]
in the field where they are going to study the
hen when they come in October, Arizona
studies their student, it was said, design
montante that anti much with Bayern and
sugar and stand up that if you can
understand the pen, you this side in
Griñón, a hack for you are going to destroy the
rage in your own heart forever,
forging the dollar for 100 dollars,
ok ok for 100 dollars,
it's a difficult question, so it's not
easy,
why does the magic
ander, because that magic pill
has the courage, the reality is
doctors who fear and internalize the money,
shopping too, and shopping has the
money,
James, that you throw in the gamble, choose here in
Madrid and in six versions, the answer is
very short in Haiti and very deep, that
Chen
Kingston,
the 50 percent commission with certain
people
in game management, here is my question
again, cool,
because Andrés Tilde did  If you understand
the pen well, there's a base area of ​​ba,
said Ivonne from the game, you'll never get
angry with this manager, he
lives in the form of perfect
$200 shoe polish because the object you're
angry with is impossible, it's
a perfect answer
and she's
going to repeat it,
you go, go with the Bose marriage counselor,
times like these, they're going to
say something like, they've also made me
GP, don't get angry with your husband, his time,
he's tired and one never, worker
stewart, the World Cup of Horrors, you know how much
work it is to watch the World Cup, it
costs hours,
I am and sandwich, he's also hungry,
guard, me home to call, you come, you
just get home, cook and that's not
enough, he can't cook for
himself anymore, journey before, you've come, hard
live, try to understand that the husband
has a very difficult life, even if in
gray, don't get angry, because in derio Spain they
sacrifice and lower the secretary
$50, what caused them this is a
marriage counselor, the spu of smart
camps, here is the
top Buddhist marriage counselor and nobody leaves, don't you  You anger
your husband or the husband because
this milestone exists does not exist I will become a
Nazi you are angry with nothing it
is the same immediately
if you want to be angry with your husband what
is the forest go to the forest and to the tri
yell at the tree it is not your p you are a
fool and tomic if it does not exist I there of
naksa send links and you are yelling at
someone that they do not exist bestel do they understand
in wenchuan country faith with and the
country and when one country fights against
another country in the day of carly shay enemy and
the other country is our enemy enemy does
not exist abiword all the
wars world work to the second world war
juan android measure and vote 100 million
people died of origin die in
eastern for sainz a 30 million
died in the eastern part of China you
in m who is the enemy
9 exists never has existed min English
all have no meaning it is
meaningless the war between countries
between countries is minitas it makes no sense
what is not living there is nobody there
efe jmr with whom you are fighting you
walk away with other countries and still
the other countries bad people com for
me  You're not going to fight the other
country if you understand that the bad people
in the other country come from you.
Wolf takes the dead people from the
other countries where the company is. You're going to
fix the bad people in the other
country from where they come from and keep going. It's
active that before they understand you. You do
n't stop military-type
bad people by killing them. Word baby
volcano family. More bad people are going to
come here and artifacts. You have to
fix them from where they come from, from the source
where it comes from. Soya pertinent perfect answer.
[Music] I
was their answer and this.
[Music]
Why you can is okay because you can
stop your rage and lately it's worse.
In the supreme method to stop your
anger and placing stent is understanding that
ASB in their name is that the husband who is
called
there, tunic. I didn't do anything and everything
exists, doesn't exist and that doesn't exist cannot
exist and doesn't exist, has never
existed. Blessed. Listen
every time in your life. Get every
time in your life up to now from the
place where you have been angry or
identified to do this traffic, even
in the traffic,
the great hail that fell in Guadalajara
that  They got upset,
they're upset about something delicate, and a
mayday. You made that hail
outside, you should be upset with
yourselves, and a mayday. Craft, you
made the traffic, and a mayday. You
made the pollution, and meta. I was
until you made the husband
stupid. When you're here, you understand,
Bauen, and what dengue. But when you get angry
and a lightbulb you forgot on Wi-Fi
and you say I didn't do anything because before, they
understand you. I'm not from the center of this
answer. We can, yes, we can say, know,
without a past, I had NGR, and that it's impossible to
get angry, and firm MDP. If you remember, the
pen is impossible, it's impossible, I had
on Wii, getting angry is a mission of yours.
If you don't misunderstand where
Fort's husband came from, therefore, he must see himself as a
toy among all the people who get
angry.
Spock, Erin, standing, they are forgetting
Fort's pen, therefore, if he loves her, it's
sad. He must be
shown the pen again and again
and again.
Spears said that Chivas, especially
for what it is, and another, this, which is
truly also
magical. Now you know, moment, we have seven
minutes, Abbas Station, so  that distance
from these classes are not easy to be
in class being hand this factor and it is I
sat in classes at the monastery
for 30 years two hours for having classes I did
n't live but it's without classes four
hours without a break
to go to the bathroom
I made a promise in my heart when I
become a software master of this
animal to suffer because it's not active
anymore elite snow I had to do with
has quite a bit of
reading conversion money people can be doubt said Hervé
trouble in the world
camps from that and eastern and of all
the problems in the world come from not
understanding the pen software finish the
protection Frank of guardians touring
there are also so first we had a
student appointment to deny him an area
must put Ryder abdomen but the
rhyme writer follow
water skill lastly he said and if I don't grow
that I'm going to quote you sharp in pure be
present and Bojan said the same touch
conversion button Tiananmen you know if
per share and skin stains a person
who understands the pen that no can't get
angry
if they remember the pen in the kitchen the
yoke
and they won't
and you
[Music] I'll
kill you
This week, now very important for this
week, I love you, I kill you as software,
love it, it's antel post, understand up in
the trailer, what am I supposed to
do until I understand the pen all
the time and you're not singing before Mike
and Mary, Kate, trace, if there's anything I
can do until my
pen memory strengthens and becomes very
strong against the Celtic, it sneaks in and jazz, I
'm not so much anymore,
sometimes there are short-term methods,
you put short-term methods
in play, it indicates, see,
and what we're going to cover this
week was 2 people, for those people
who don't get close to playing the kitchen, who ca
n't remember the pen in the
kitchen, we're going to cover the temper, and
we're going to cover the temporary methods of
Juniors and Move
Engel Frontera, Jimena Marín, they're not going to
remove, they're not going to take away the rage of
the human mind, says Mary, with knowing how to
put these are marriage counselor methods
by field, for example
[Music]
temporary method number 2, Tom Coughlin from
Quiché,
that's a good method, you
can't Santander and touch, but  Sometimes
it's okay in holy genetics allows a
success
sometimes you have to take a break from
your literal relationship and catamarca troy
extra because you can't control yourself in
dividing word being deaths because it keeps getting
worse and worse your interest in
Buddhism with each Disney we teach this
method sun-times sometimes and artistic
go to your mom's for two days ok and
look luckily it will help you for a
short period of time
when there is proof but it won't help
the problem show first in one star and the
first thing we're going to study this week
this week I did short term mates are
temporary methods and sahuayo in emery
camps this is what you hear with
marriage counselors media to
twitter break maybe you have to take
a break code
go to your mom's takes you away from the
kids transmit and futuristic pizza and
latex step that I eat pizza for two days
that instant break sometimes you need
a break that snacks verifix suddenly it won't
solve the problem so that
this space but it gives you some space in
figueres paste baby i member duke and if
you have a little space maybe
you'll remember to apply software that doesn't
I would be here if there is a fer wave. We're going to
study six different ways,
Xytex, my space, to take some
space. Demon, take the space.
Then when you take that space, what I need,
MDP, can you remember the pen? Okay,
software that I will need, we're going to
study it, the sixways tickets in space, 6
ways to get that space. Okay, I'll do that. That's all
for this morning. That's all
for this morning. If my daughter, man, and
in 2000
have any